PREETHA MATHAN

CUSTOMER RELATIONSHIP MANAGER

NO.28 Ohm Siva Sakthi Nagar, Saravanampatti coimbtore-641035.

+91 7397739738 mail id: pre000731@gmail.com

Career Objective

Experienced and Energetic of customer relationship manager with over 3 years. Obtain a job use my exceptional interpersonal and communication skills to resolve customer issues and foster a positive relationship between the customers and company.

Additional Skills

- Tele Marketing
- Product sales
- Communication Skills
- Customer care
- Management Skills
- Customer Service
- System Handling

Work Experience

Product Sales – Bharath Tvs Showroom:(2012-2013)Palladam.

- Vehicle sales to customer
- To monitor Customer Satisfied
- Handling PSF Telecalls
- Vehicle Parts sales and Stock Maintenance
- Data Entry.

Sales Team Leader – Anaamalais Agencies Pvt ltd Coimbatore.(2013-2018)

- set sales target and motivate sales team
- Keep informed of new product and services
- Recruit, train and coach the sales team
- Prepare sales Reports.
- Assist managers in sales strategy Development.

Customer Relationship Manager 5k car care Pvt ltd (2019-2021)

- Resolving customer complaints quickly and efficiently
- keeping customers updated on the latest products in order to increase sales
- expanding customers base up selling and cross selling.
- Overseeing the relationship with customer handles by team.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:

Course	Institution	Board/University	Year of passing	Percentage obtained
BBM	Tiruppur Kumaran College	Bharathiyar university.	May 2011	79%
HSC	Govt Hr sec school. Palladam	State Board	April 2008	60%
SSLC	Govt High school. Palladam	State Board	April 2006	75%

SEMINARS AND CONFERENCES

- Participated international Seminar at *Tirupur kumaran College* on the topic of "*REBOOTING STRATEGIES FOR GLOBAL RECESSION*" on the year of 2010
- seminars on public ralations and Marketing.